welchallyn.com 2016-03-25

# Privacy Policy

_October 6, 2015_

Welch Allyn is committed to protecting the security and privacy of your personal information. Therefore, we conduct our business in compliance with all applicable laws concerning data security and privacy. The policy outlined below was created to inform you as to how we will handle any information submitted on our site, and to detail the security of our site. Please read it carefully.

Welch Allyn complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Welch Allyn has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Welch Allyn’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

The privacy policy outlined below is applicable to all sites on the World Wide Web owned and operated by Welch Allyn.

### Topics Covered in this Privacy Policy

  * Information Collected
  * Use of Collected Information
  * Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically
  * Security of Collected Information
  * Use of Cookies
  * Links to Other Sites
  * Contacting Us
  * Changes to This Policy

Welch Allyn will not collect any personal information about you (i.e. your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal information.

If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have previously submitted this information and would like for us to remove it, please click on “Contact Us” located on the Welch Allyn homepage. We will make all reasonable attempts to delete your information from our files.

This website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children. Our products are intended for use by providers of healthcare, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.

###   
Use of Collected Information

The information you supply will be used to respond to inquiries, notify you of promotions and announcements if you have previously provided your permission, or to supply you with requested information on products and services.

Welch Allyn will not sell your personal information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We may share information with our business partners.  

### Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically

There are some instances in which we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. For example, we may document the type of computer operating system you are using or the type of Internet browser you are operating.

We will not sell your non-personal information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We may share this non-personal information with our business partners.

###   
Security of Collected Information

Welch Allyn utilizes current technical security measures to safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure with respect to business transactions being conducted through Welch Allyn websites.

###   
Use of Cookies

When you view the Welch Allyn website we may store some data on your computer in the form of a “cookie” which may be used to create an improved website. If you do not want to receive cookies, please refer to your browser instructions and configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

###   
Links to Other Sites

The Welch Allyn website may contain links to other websites. Although we try to link to other sites that embrace our high level of respect for your privacy, we cannot be certain of the content, security, or privacy practices used by these sites.

###   
Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please refer to the “Contact Us” page. We welcome any suggestions you may have.

###   
Changes to this Policy

Please refer to this privacy policy periodically for any variations. Although we reserve the right to modify this policy at any time, we will post any major changes on this website.
